

## **Profile**

My name is Erick Hernandez and I'm from Mexico City.

I enjoy creating things that live on the internet. My interest in web development started back in 2018 when I decided to try editing custom Tumblr themes — turns out hacking together a custom reblog button taught me a lot about HTML & CSS!

Fast-forward to today, and I've had the privilege of working as a freelance developer at <u>an advertising agency</u>, <u>a start-up</u>. My main focus these days is building accessible, inclusive products and digital experiences for a variety of clients.

# **Employment History**

Front-end Developer, Upstament, 245 8th Avenue #1030, NYC 10011

JUNE 2020 - JULY 2021

- Developed and maintained code for in-house and client websites primarily using HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, and Reacy Native
- Manually tested sites in various browsers and mobile devices to ensure cross-browser compatibility and responsiveness
- Clients included JetBlue, Lovesac, U.S. Cellular, U.S. Department of Defense, and more
- Multi-platform application development with React Native

## Front-end Developer, Pixelbot, 600-212 King St. W., Toronto, ON, Canada

JUNE 2021 - PRESENT

- Collaborated to create strategic initiaticves to design, code, and test solutions.
- Effectively coded software changes and alterations based on specific design specifications.
- Created, communicated, and managed project plans.
- Multi-platform application development with React Native

# **Education**

certificate, UNITEC Campus Sur, Mexico City

JANUARY 2022 - PRESENT

Software and Network Engineering

#### **Details**

Mexico City +525564786032 yerickk8@gmail.com

#### Links

**Portfolio** 

### **Skills**

React

React Native

AngularJS

JavaScript

Node.js

Express.js

jQuery

Python

Django

HTML & CSS

Bootstrap

Git

GitHub

MySQL

MongoDB

## Languages

English

#### **Hobbies**

coding - reading - exercise